plum.io 2019-09-18

# Plum Terms of Service

This Privacy Policy is intended to help you better understand how we collect, use, store and disclose your personal information. By using the services of Plum.io, Inc. (“Plum”), you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and, as applicable, the Plum Terms of Service. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to reflect changes to our privacy practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy on this Website. By continuing to use Plum services after these changes are posted, you agree to the revised policy.

### Information that is gathered from visitors

Where registration is required, the visitor's email, first name, last name and a username will be stored on the server. Job seekers applying for jobs through our system, or entering the Plum system through a third-party partner, may be required to provide additional personal information such as phone number, address, as well as a resume and/or cover letter.

We also collect and store log files on our web server, which includes details such as a visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.

We also use cookies, a unique identifier sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. This is done for the following reasons:

  * We use cookies to recognize your device and provide you with a personalized experience on our websites, or otherwise through the Services.
  * Third party advertising company may also use cookies for tracking purposes.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.

### How the Information is used

The personal information collected is used to enhance the visitor's experience when using the website to display personalized content and possibly advertising.

E-mail addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to any 3rd parties without the express permission of the user.

The Plum service equips employers with the data to hire, develop, retain, and promote workers. When taking an assessment for an employer that uses the Plum service, you are consenting to Plum and that employer to view your name, email address, personal information contained within a resume and/or cover letter, and assessment scores. Additional consent is needed from you before those data can be shared beyond the entities you have already given consent to when applying and/or taking the Plum assessment.

Consent that you give to third-party partners (job boards, applicant tracking systems, etc.) with regards to information stored on their servers or access granted may entitle that third-party to data stored on Plum servers. The most common case is an application through a job board that sends the job seeker to the Plum Assessment. This job board has its own policies regarding privacy and terms of use. By agreeing to use the Plum Service through one of these third-parties, you also agree to allow said third-party access to your Plum data.

E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us or our affiliates as well as for support purposes.

### Retention of Information

Plum retains the personal information provided upon registration (e.g., name, email address, cover letter/resume) for legitimate business purposes and to comply with the law, except when we receive a valid erasure request or a period of 7 years has passed since a user has been active. You may request to cancel your account by emailing [privacy@plum.io](mailto:privacy@plum.io) and providing your first name, last name, and email address. Plum may contact you after 7 years of inactivity to verify that your personal information should be deleted.

### Accessing Your Information

You may access most of your personal information under the About tab of the My Account section when you log into the latest version of the Plum service. You may also request to access your personal information by emailing [privacy@plum.io](mailto:privacy@plum.io) and providing your first name, last name, and email address.

### Visitor Options

If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe through the unsubscribe footer in all emails, or by replying to these messages with a request for opt-out. In addition a user can request deletion of their marketing records and all associated website tracking (cookies) by emailing [privacy@plum.io](mailto:privacy@plum.io).

### Security of Your Personal Information

Plum follows industry recognized standards on information security management to safeguard your information. Our information security systems apply to people, processes and the technology we employ.

### Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)

As part of our service, we may transfer your personal information to other regions, including to Canada. If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. If you wish to exercise these rights, please reach out to us using the contact information below.

### Control Over Your Personal Information

We understand that you have rights over your personal information and we take reasonable steps to allow you to access, correct, amend, delete, port, or limit the use of your personal information.

If you have any questions about your personal information or this policy, or if you would like to make a complaint about how Plum’s processes your personal data, please contact Plum by email at [privacy@plum.io](mailto:privacy@plum.io) or by using the contact details below:

**Plum.io, Inc.**  
ATTN: Chief Privacy Officer  
550 Parkside Drive  
Building B, Unit 1  
Waterloo, ON N2L 5V4  
Canada
